

# JESSE H. OUDOM

## JUNIOR WEB DEVELOPER

- in https://www.linkedin.com/in/jesseoudom/
- https://github.com/joudom
- jesse\_oudom@yahoo.com
- +310-465-6420
- Hampton, GA
- https://joudom.github.io/JesseOudom/

### **Summary:**

Motivated full-stack developer with project management experience and familiarity with high-paced environments requiring collaboration and communication.

Driven to build applications as part of a team to improve the modern world as well as the future.

#### Front-End Skills:

- HTML5
- CSS3
- Bootstrap 5
- JavaScript
- jQuery
- Δ ΙΔΧ
- ReactJS
- Create React App
- Redux

#### **Back-End Skills:**

- Node.js
- Express.js
- PostgreSQL
- Git
- REST
- Bcrypt
- Sequelize

#### **Education History**



# **High School Diploma**

West High School - Torrance, CA Year of Graduation: 2009

GPA: 2.8

#### Certifications



## **Certificate of Completion**

DigitalCrafts - Atlanta, GA Year of Graduation: 2022

- Full-Stack Web Development
- 26-week bootcamp covering modern front-end and back-end technologies

#### **Work Experience**



# Kuehne + Nagel Inc May 2022 - Present

Customs Entry Writer East Point, GA

- Process entries for customs release
- Review documentation for US CBP compliance



# **DigitalCrafts** June 2022 - December 2022

Full-Stack Web Developer Atlanta, GA

### **LocalEyes**

https://github.com/joudom/LocalEyes

- React application allowing users to upload & post deals found in their local area.
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, ReactJS, Git, Node.js, Express.js, Bcrypt, Cors, Google Maps API

#### <u>Drink-182</u>

https://github.com/joudom/Drink-182

- Front-end application allowing users to explore cocktail recipes & also meals to possibly pair with.
- HTML, CSS, Bootstrap, JavaScript, jQuery, Git, Text-to-Speech Reader



# **Fluence Energy** March 2021 - May 2022

Logistics Specialist

Alpharetta, GA

- Global operations & project management
- Arrange transport of goods to various sites